spcnet.tv 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy - spcnet.tv

spcnet.tv takes the privacy of its users seriously. Generally, you can browse through our Website without giving us any information about yourself (including your email address). When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information. If we decide to change our privacy policy for this Website, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

### Information Collection

We collect personal information (such as your name, email address, and any other details you provide to us that identifies you as an individual) from you when you submit a request for information or when you submit your details for any other reason. Personal information will only be collected with your consent. When you browse our Website, we may also log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our Website you visit and how long you spend here. We do not link your IP address to any other personal information that you send to us. Like many other websites, we may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the Website (see section 6. Cookies) Save for the use of cookies, we do not automatically log data or collect data apart from information you specifically provide to us. 

### Use Of Information We Collect

We will use your information for several general purposes including: fulfilling any requests for information or services placed by you, processing any other transactions authorised by you, personalising your experience on our Website, keeping you up to date with news about spcnet.tv, our products and services, and providing other information to you which we think you may find of interest. Your personal information shall not be used for any other purposes. 

### Who May Process Data

Your personal information may be processed by us in accordance with this privacy policy. We take all reasonable care to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal data. Personal information will not be sold or transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your prior consent. 

### Security Measures

We are serious about guarding the security of your personal information that we have under our control from unauthorised access, improper use and disclosure, unauthorised destruction or accidental loss. However, we cannot guarantee the protection of your personal data as due to the nature of the Internet, the Website is theoretically accessible by any user of the World Wide Web. You should be aware that when you disclose personal information on the Website it may be collected by another user and may result in unsolicited messages from other Internet users. 

### Session Variables

Some sections of our website require your information to be stored in what's known as a session variable. Session variables exist for the length of your visit (or in the case of our client login, until you log out). 

### Access and Changes to your Personal Information

At your request, we will use reasonable efforts to update / correct personal information previously submitted by you. You may also request that we cease processing the personal information we have about you and that we delete your personal information from our database or records. However, it may be impossible to delete your information without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions. 

Please address your requests to delete your personal information to us at the Contact Us page and insert "Delete Account" as the subject heading. Please state your name and email address for identification purposes. 

We will only perform the activities outlined above to the extent that such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests. 

### Changes to this Policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. When such a change is made we will post a revised version on the Website. It is your responsibility to view this privacy policy from time to time to be aware of any such change. Your continued use of the Website will indicate your agreement to any such change. 

### For further information

If you have any further enquiries or concerns about our privacy policy please email us at the Contact Us page.
